{
  "እንቆቅልሽ": [
    {
      "question": "asdfasdfa",
      "answers": [
        "adfasf",
        "xcadcsc",
        "dvsdvs",
        "sdfsdfs"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "xcadcsc"
    },
    {
      "question": "dwferv",
      "answers": [
        "sfvvds",
        "dfbvdfb",
        "dfrtgrg",
        "dfgerve"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "dfrtgrg"
    },
    {
      "question": "uhbhbgbgb",
      "answers": [
        "bhbhbhb",
        "hbhbhbhgb",
        "hbhbhbhb",
        "bgvvvf"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "hbhbhbhb"
    },
    {
      "question": " bg g vf f",
      "answers": [
        "nfvddfv",
        "sdfgverv",
        "dfgh",
        "fghj"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "dfgh"
    },
    {
      "question": "xdcfgvbhnjmk",
      "answers": [
        "crvghjn",
        "xsdcfgvn",
        "cfgvbh",
        "cfgvbh"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "xsdcfgvn"
    },
    {
      "question": "xdcfvgbhjn",
      "answers": [
        "xdcfgvbhnj",
        "dcfvgbhjnmk",
        "xdvhjn",
        "hjnmk,l"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "dcfvgbhjnmk"
    }
  ],
  "gvgvgvgvbbbb": [
    {
      "question": "awfwefwe",
      "answers": [
        "sdgewfgw",
        "wefgqwerf",
        "sdfgwerfg",
        "segerg"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "wefgqwerf"
    },
    {
      "question": "bhnjnjn",
      "answers": [
        "sdfvsd",
        "ergerge",
        "serger",
        "wegewr"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "ergerge"
    },
    {
      "question": "xdcfgvbhnjm",
      "answers": [
        "fgvbhjnm",
        "dcfvbn",
        " nm",
        "cfgvbhn"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": " nm"
    },
    {
      "question": "xdcfgvbhn",
      "answers": [
        "cvgbhjn",
        "cfvgbjn",
        "dcfvgbhnj",
        "dcfvgbhn"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "cfvgbjn"
    },
    {
      "question": "xdcfgvbhn",
      "answers": [
        "c vbn",
        "cfvgbh",
        "cfvgbh",
        "cfgvbh"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "cfvgbh"
    },
    {
      "question": "cfvgbhnj",
      "answers": [
        "cfgvbhjnmk",
        "cfgvbhnj",
        "cfgvbhnj",
        "cfvgbnhj"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "cfgvbhnj"
    }
  ]
}